# HEATHER CAMPBELL

՛്

heather.campbell1212@gmail.com



(270) 585-0754

0

Jamestown, KY 42629

## PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

Goal-oriented Junior Web Developer and seasoned Sales Executive brings strong commitment to collaboration and solutions-oriented problem-solving. Use various web design packages to develop custom-crafted, customer-focused websites and designs. Committed to high standards of customer satisfaction, user experience, and usability. Lends detailed knowledge of customer relations to increase visibility.

#### **SKILLS**

- HTML5
- CSS3
- SASS
- Bootstrap
- JavaScript
- Chrome Dev Tools
- React
- Git
- Terminal
- Web development projects
- Programming
- Microsoft Office
- Relationship-Building
- Teamwork
- Excellent work ethic
- Verbal and written communication
- Planning and Coordination
- Sales Closing
- Customer Relations
- Sales expertise
- Account development

#### LINKS

- <a href="https://www.linkedin.com/in/heather-campbell-b45b6515/">https://www.linkedin.com/in/heather-campbell-b45b6515/</a>
- http://www.bcskills.org/
- https://heatherncampbell.github.io/

#### **WORK HISTORY**

## **ERA Real Solutions - Real Estate Agent**

West Chester, OH 05/2016 - 04/2017

- Managed contracts, negotiations and all aspects of sales to finalize purchases and exceed customer expectations.
- Generated leads for sales through cold calls and referrals.

## LCS - Sales Executive

Loveland, OH 07/2005 - 06/2015

- Increased revenue by implementing effective sales strategies in all aspects of sales cycle process from prospecting leads through close.
- Managed entire sales cycle across customer accounts, proposing and closing sales to achieve total revenue growth, profit and customer satisfaction plans.
- Presented products to clients using dynamic presentations and practical use-case scenarios.

## **EDUCATION**

BCSkills Academy (January 2021-Present) Glasgow, KY

## **Web Development**

 Coursework in HTML5, CSS3, SASS, Bootstrap, JavaScript, Chrome Dev Tools, React, Git and Terminal.

## W.W.Grainger - Government Account Manager

Dayton, OH • 03/2002 - 06/2004

- Analyzed past sales data and team performance to develop realistic quarterly sales goals.
- Directed work of efficient administrative team maintaining accurate sales, inventory and order documentation.
- Executed local, regional and national marketing and branding initiatives to drive sales within existing and prospective accounts.